Preliminary Inventory to the Dumitru Danielopol Papers, 1940-1973
Hoover Institution Archives
- International Scene - Is U.S. Hurting NATO?, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), July 13, 1967
- International Scene - Just a Little More Rope, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 19, 1968
- International Scene - Kremlin Plays Politics, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 13, 1967
- International Scene - Lenin and Stalin Set Red Pattern, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), November 25, 1967
- International Scene - A Look at Student Riots, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 17, 1968
- International Scene - The March of Truth, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 3, 1968
- International Scene - Marxism Record Reveals Little, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 3, 1967
- International Scene - The Marxist Man Isn't, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 12, 1968
- International Scene - A Message to Hanoi..., Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 23, 1969
- International Scene - New Book Examines Cold War Strategy, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), March 27, 1965
- International Scene - A New Look at Cuba, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), October 17, 1968
- International Scene - Nixon Bring a Change, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), March 13, 1969
- International Scene - Nuclear Pact May Need Closer Look, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), September 23, 1968
- International Scene - On Propaganda Front, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 18, 1969
- International Scene - One Plus for Romania, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 27, 1968
- International Scene - One Woman's War, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), September 8, 1967
- International Scene - 'Only Five Kings Left', Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 27, 1967
- International Scene - A Page Out of History, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 20, 1969
- International Scene - Philosophy Has New Tune, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), November 15, 1969
- International Scene - The President Was Right, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), May 15, 1970
- International Scene - Propaganda Serves Red Line in France, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), May 22, 1967
- International Scene - Question For Intellectuals, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 13, 1968
- International Scene - Question in Britain: Can Wilson Go On?, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), July 8, 1969
- International Scene - Red China Issue Fades, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), September 25, 1968
- International Scene - Religion Remains Target in Russia, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), September 23, 1969
- International Scene - Restless Hungarian Test Russian Bear, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), June 9, 1972
- International Scene - Senator Brooke's First Worth Wait, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), April 5, 1967
- International Scene - Small Nations Use Caution With Peking, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 11, 1967
- International Scene - So Says Professor Toynbee, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), July 21, 1965
- International Scene - Solace For the Enemy, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), February 20, 1968
- International Scene - Soviet Massacre Recalled, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), March 24, 1970
- International Scene - Spain Pays Dividend, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), June 19, 1967
- International Scene - 'Talk to the People', Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), June 16, 1967
- International Scene - Talks Won't Alter U.S., French Views, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), May 16, 1968
- International Scene - That's What She Said, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 16, 1970
- International Scene - They Freely Advise But Stay 'Out of It', Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), October 7, 1967
- International Scene - Thoughts To Ponder From Tunisian Chief, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), September 15, 1967
- International Scene - Trade With Enemy, However You Say It, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 20, 1967
- International Scene - Trouble in the Family, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), July 15, 1965
- International Scene - Trouble With Tourists, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), April 4, 1970
- International Scene - Two Men and a Nation, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), May 14, 1970
- International Scene - U.S. Silent On Czechs, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), August 7, 1968
- International Scene - Veep and His Friends, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), February 19, 1970
- International Scene - Viet Cong Running Down, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), February 26, 1969
- International Scene - Vietnam: Testing Ground, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 29, 1970
- International Scene - Vietnam Question Remains Pertinent, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), September 29, 1969
- International Scene - War Over Cyprus Would Suit Kremlin, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), December 18, 1967
- International Scene - Warsaw Pact Is Dead, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 3, 1969
- International Scene - West German Air Smells Like Money, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), May 31, 1967
- International Scene - What Is 'Neutrality', Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), March 7, 1969
- International Scene - What Is Soviet Goal?, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), November 19, 1969
- International Scene - Where Was McCarthy, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), January 29, 1968
- International Scene - Will Consular Treaty Soften Kremlin Line?, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), March 29, 1967
- International Scene - 'With No Compassion', Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), April 2, 1970
- International Scene - Wolf at Kremlin Door?, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), July 17, 1967
- International Scene - The Words Are Familiar, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), October 14, 1966
- International Scene - Writers Defy Kremlin, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), February 24, 1968
- International Scene - Yugoslavs Irk Kremlin, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), June 5, 1970
- Iran Thrust Into Buffer Position in Middle East, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 16, 1970
- Iran's 'White' Solution, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), July 2, 1970
- Iron Curtain Lands Keep Sense of Humor, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 3, 1970
- Is Romania Independent of Moscow?, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 21, 1965
- Is Russia Really Worker's Paradise?, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), November 7, 1967
- Is There Revolution in Russia?, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 10, 1972
- Is This a Sick Society?, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), November 1, 1968
- Isn't It Time We Identify Our Enemy?, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), April 29, 1968
- It Takes More Than White Hat To Change a Communist, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), December 13, 1966
- It Take Two to End Cold War, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), March 8, 1967
- It Wasn't a Coincidence, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 13, 1965
- Italy Open to Communist Attack, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 17, 1969 (Box 6)
- It's Far From Over, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), April 1, 1970
- It's Time to Face Facts on U.N. and Red Threat, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 10, 1964
- JFK's Views On Vietnam, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), March 26, 1968
- Julian Amery May Soon Return to British Political Picture, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 14, 1969
- Kennedy Ireland Jibe Comes to Haunt Him, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 3, 1972
- Kennedy's Strange Speech, Illinois State Journal, October 4, 1969
- King Says - Moscow Call Tune in Romania, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), July 9, 1965
- Knight in Armor? Teddy Turns Toward '76, South Bay Daily Breeze (Torrance, Calif.), November 14, 1972
- 'Knock-on-Door' Terror is Resumed in Romania, The San Diego Union (Calif.), January 13, 1965
- Korean-Type Settlement?, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), March 21, 1969
- Kremlin Faces Red Over Unmet Goals, The San Diego Union (Calif.), January 1, 1970
- Kremlin is Trying to Muffle Cries of Freedom in Russia, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 21, 1969
- Kremlin Planners Out-Maneuver U.S., The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 10, 1964
- Kremlin Seeking Scapegoats For Defeat of It's Athletes, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), January 20, 1969
- Kremlin Study - Russ Still Dream of Soviet Europe, Alhambra Post-Advocate (Calif.), May 29, 1967
- Kremlin's Face is Red as U.S. Stand Toughens, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 8, 1965
- Labor Party is Commie Goal, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), July 28, 1970
- Labor Poses Problems for Reds, The San Diego Union (Calif.), April 9, 1972
- Labor Shortage Adds to Soviet Farm Problem, The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 8, 1972
- Latin Turning Left Wing Trend, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), September 23, 1972
- Latvian Reds Call For Help, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 28, 1972
- 'Left' Finds Opposite Czech Effect, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), March 12, 1970
- Legitimacy of the Viet Reds, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), March 2, 1967
- Lippmann Proposal Boggles Imagination, Elgin Courier-News (Illinois), November 7, 1967
- Little Cause For Joy in Kremlin, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 20, 1967
- 'Logic' of Political Thinkers Is Sometimes Disconcerting, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), March 15, 1968
- London Daily Cites U.S. Conservative Movement, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 21, 1964
- Londoners Like Johnson, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 24, 1965
- Look at Americans - Life in A Goldfish Bowl, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), July 6, 1970
- 'Lucky' Marinescu's Story Gives True Picture of Communism, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 13, 1968
- McGovern Consistent in His Inconsistency, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), September 21, 1972
- McGovern Losing Exiles - Cuban-Americans Are Upset, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), August 23, 1972
- McGovern's Charge a Shameless Smear, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), November 2, 1972
- McNamara's Folly, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), May 6, 1969
- Malraux Plan Needs Look, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 24, 1972
- Man Who Directs the USIA, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), October 15, 1972
- Many Can Advise Youth of Communism Meaning, The San Diego Union (Calif.), September 4, 1969
- Marxism Called Dead as Economic System, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), May 21, 1968
- Marxism Needs a New 'Image', Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), December 27, 1966
- Marxist Agriculture Fails Test, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), September 16, 1972
- Masters of Chaos Menace the West, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 14, 1968
- Melina Mercouri's 'Democracy' Is Communism In Disguise, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), May 22, 1968
- Moscow Fears Anti-Red Group in West Germany, The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 7, 1970
- Moscow Sensitive to Attacks - Kremlin Edgy Over Peking Visit, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 4, 1972
- Nasser Hearing 'Nyet' From Russian Friends, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 27, 1966
- Nations Impaired Credibility Is Causing Deep Concern, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 8, 1969
- New Conservative Trend Is Apparent in Suburbs, The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 3, 1964
- New Johnson Headache - Problem of Viet Nam, The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 27, 1974
- New Law in Romania Dangerous, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 3, 1972
- New Look at East-West Trade, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 6, 1967
- The New Nixon Success, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), July 22, 1968
- Nex Tax Imprisons Russian Jews, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), September 7, 1972
- New Trouble Flares in Czechoslovakia, Illinois State Journal, January 6, 1968
- 1968 Ethics Regarding War Ignored, The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 22, 1972
- Nixon Paper On Vietnam Makes Sense, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), August 6, 1968
- Nixon Policy, Personality Boost America Abroad, The San Diego Union (Calif.), February 16, 1970
- Nixon Stands Tall As President, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), May 19, 1972
- Nixon Will Find Romania a Nationalistic Red State, The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 27, 1969
- Nixon Will Hold Four Aces in Coming Summit Talks, The San Diego Union (Calif.), May 6, 1969
- Nixon Worrying Russians, Illinois State Journal, July 27, 1968
- Nixon's Image Is Remarkable After First Month in Office, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 23, 1969
- Nixon's Popularity Abroad, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), January 9, 1970
- No Aid For Romania Until She Shapes Up, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), February 14, 1972
- No Democracy in Ideological Monopoly - Yugoslavian Sees Red Always, Illinois State Journal, November 9, 1967
- No License Needed to Be Politician, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 2, 1966
- No Time to Relax Our Vigilance, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), December 29, 1966
- North Viets Still Want Coalition, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), January 10, 1970
- Offbeat Diary - Jesse Owens' Blitzkrieg Hit Adolf at '36 Olympics, Evening Tribune (San Diego, Calif.), July 23, 1970
- One Dividend - French Eyes Opened By May's Violence, South Bay Daily Breeze (Torrance, Calif.), August 26, 1968
- 'Operation Suicide' is Book Every American Should Read, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), July 31, 1967
- Opium Now a Weapon of War, South Bay Daily Breeze (Torrance, Calif.), April 7, 1969
- Ousting Greece Pleased Reds, Illinois State Journal, January 3, 1970
- Out of Les Caves - Scum of Paris Smears Sorbonne's Good Name, South Bay Daily Breeze (Torrance, Calif.), June 20, 1968
- Over South Africa - Critics Zero In on RFK, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), September 7, 1966
- Pact Maneuvers Fail to Unify Red Bloc, The San Diego Union (Calif.), May 31, 1969
- Pages of History Filled With Shame, The San Diego Union (Calif.), October 23, 1966
- Paris Talks Offer Third Chance to Curb Red Push, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 2, 1968
- Part of Plan - Communists Delight in Moscow Summit, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 19, 1972
- The Past Lives Again in Memories - A Man's Thoughts Are Turned Toward Home on Christmas, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), December 25, 1966
- The People Can Save Freedom's Radio Voices, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 27, 1972
- People of Greece Hate Red, Monrovia Daily News-Post (Calif.), June 19, 1967
- Philosophy Change - '64 in Limelight, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), August 7, 1968
- Platform Language is Clear, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), August 25, 1972
- Plaudits For General De Gaulle, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), July 9, 1968
- Policy Diagreement - Feud Disrupts Captive Nations Group, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), October 11, 1965
- Polish Pot Boiling Again, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 21, 1972
- The Political Scene - An Answer Is Awaited, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), July 9, 1965
- Politics in France Excite British More Than Their Own, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), July 7, 1969
- Prague Commies Clamp the Lid Down, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois)
- Praises Humphrey, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), October 24, 1969
- President Got Support He Needed, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 22, 1972
- Pressure Being Put on Senate - Genocide Issue is Spotlighted, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), March 29, 1965
- The Problem of Vietnam, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), January 10, 1969
- Problems Mount - Without Soviet Aid Castro Would Be Out, Elgin Courier-News (Illinois), July 19, 1972
- Profit Motive the Answer, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 31, 1972
- Prophetic Words From Back in '42, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), August 28, 1967
- Protestors Don't Read History, Illinois State Journal, November 6, 1969
- Pueblo Incident Has Forced Americans to Face Reality, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 9, 1968
- Purpose of U.S. Stand in Vietnam Made Clear, The San Diego Union (Calif.), October 5, 1967
- Pushers Face Death Sentence - Iran's War Against Opium Relentless, Illinois State Journal, June 4, 1970
- Questions Have Been Raised By 'L' Affaire Manchester', Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), January 5, 1967
- Questions Romania's Boom, Illinois State Journal, August 16, 1969
- Radicals the Same All Over the World, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), January 31, 1972
- Radio Free Europe is Dimished Force, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 30, 1970
- Radio Free Europe is Hurting America, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 28, 1969
- Radio Free Europe May Become Victim of Johnson's Policies, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), January 18, 1968
- The Rape of Poland, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), November 24, 1969
- Raps Unrest - Foreign Student Lauds the U.S., The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 10, 1969
- Raul Castro Praises Kennedy Report, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 9, 1966
- The Real Lenin, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), March 31, 1970
- Rebirth of Nationalism Could Crack the Kremlin, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), March 24, 1969
- Red Army's Power Grows, Illinois State Journal, April 12, 1969
- Red Bloc Exile's View - Twisting U.S. Tiger's Tail Seen As Global Pastime, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 9, 1964
- Red China Torn By Dissent, Purges, Elgin Courier-News (Illinois), October 25, 1966
- Red Fete Turned Sour, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), November 24, 1968
- Red Lands Are Poor Credit Risk, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), January 9, 1967
- Red Monolith Changed, But Aims Are Same, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), February 2, 1968
- The Red 'Paradise' - Statistics Help To Peg Price of Communism, South Bay Daily Breeze (Torrance, Calif.), September 27, 1968
- Red Propaganda is Clear, Glendale News-Press (Calif.), February 27, 1967
- Red Propaganda Message to GIs Quotes Senators, The San Diego Union (Calif.), March 9, 1968
- Red Rule in East Europe, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), March 16, 1970
- Red Satellite Nations Growing More Restive, The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 17, 1964
- Red Truth Will Out, Elgin Daily Courier-News (Illinois), October 6, 1967
- Reds Feared Busy Distorting History, The San Diego Union (Calif.), September 13, 1964
- Reds Firm On Peace Terms, Illinois State Journal, July 19, 1969
- Reds Have Not Abandoned Aim of Vietnam Victory, The San Diego Union (Calif.), April 15, 1968
- Reds Like Time Payments, South Bay Daily Breeze (Torrance, Calif.)
- Reds May Seek Tourist Trade, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 27, 1967
- Reds Still Distort the Truth, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 9, 1972
- Reds Stole Romania's 'Free' Election, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 13, 1966
- Reds to Blame as Peace Still Eludes Mankind, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 26, 1964
- Reds Will Attempt to Profit From Nixon's Visit to Romania, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), July 18, 1969
- Reds Won't Let Their Youth See U.S., The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 17, 1966
- Refugee Says Communism a Flop, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 27, 1969
- A Renegade Friend - De Gaulle, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), December 26, 1967
- Rewriting World History Doesn't Change the Fact, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 17, 1969
- Richard Nixon Must Rebuild American Image Overseas, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 20, 1968
- The Rising Tide Paper Sells a Dream, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 18, 1972
- Robert Kennedy Has Become Leading Critic of Johnson, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 30, 1967
- Romania Action is Not Moscow Split, The San Diego Union (Calif.), May 31, 1966
- Romania Clamps Down the Lid, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), November 3, 1969
- Romania is Watched For Ceausescu Course, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 23, 1967
- Romania Lowest On Totem Pole, Alhambra Post-Advocate (Calif.), April 21, 1967
- Romania Must Bare Her Economic Soul, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), September 27, 1972 (Box 7)
- Romania Put Skids Under Khrushchev?, The San Diego Union (Calif.), November 19, 1964
- Romania Rewrites History In Fear of Soviet Union, The San Diego Union (Calif.), August 31, 1968
- Romania Taxes Mourners Who Visit Cemeteries, The San Diego Union (Calif.), September 1, 1966
- Romania's Need - Economic Revamp It Can't Afford, The San Diego Union (Calif.), September 14, 1971
- Romanian Culutral Idea is Hoax, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 7, 1972
- Romanian Human Rights Should Be Trade Price, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 2, 1964
- Romanian Reds Try New Face, But Can't Forget Old Ways, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), August 21, 1969
- Romanian Reds Try To Improve Image, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), December 4, 1969
- Romanians Will Observe Sad 25th Anniversary, The San Diego Union (Calif.), February 25, 1970
- Roumanians Under Red Rule Get Factories and Not Food, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 10, 1969
- Russ Revolt Against Intelligence, Glendale News-Press (Calif.), September 13, 1967
- Russ Workers Upset Brezhnev, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), March 28, 1972
- Russia Trying to Bribe Satellites With Promises of Gold and Trade, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), June 22, 1966
- Russian Grain Buys Bears Watching, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), October 13, 1972
- Russian Prestige Has Dropped To New Low, Says Julian Amery, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), July 14, 1967
- Russians Chain Man's Freedoms, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), February 20, 1972
- Russians Could Take Lessons in Art of Winning Friends, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), December 4, 1967
- Russians Still Consider Nixon Election Possible, The San Diego Union (Calif.), April 1, 1967
- Salute to Cardinal Spellman, Alhambra Post-Advocate (Calif.), January 9, 1967
- Same Old Gimmick Over Peace 'Signal', Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), September 7, 1972
- Samizdat' Alarms Kremlin Leaders, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 29, 1972
- Schlesinger Confusing, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), April 3, 1967
- See Hand of Communist China In Creation of French Crisis, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), June 3, 1968
- Sees Dawn of a New Era, Illinois State Journal, November 16, 1968
- Sees U.S. in Financial Crisis, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), May 7, 1968
- Sellout to Reds - Democratic Platform Written in Hanoi?, Elgin Courier-News (Illinois), July 7, 1972
- Senator Humphrey Approval of Khrushchev Naive, The San Diego Union (Calif.), December 11, 1964
- Senator McCarthy on Vietnam, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), November 9, 1969
- Senator McGovern Ignores Reality, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), August 4, 1972
- Senator Mansfield's Words Are Imitation to Aggression, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), September 27, 1968
- Senator Russell on Vietnam, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), April 13, 1968
- Senator Sees Sign Nixon Plan Works, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), April 2, 1970
- Sergei Knows 'Worker Paradise', Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), August 13, 1972
- She Knows Freddom's Meaning, Burbank Daily Review (Calif.), April 25, 1967
- Sino-Soviet Romance Will Flower Again, Expert Thinks, The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 6, 1969
- The Situation in Greece, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), October 23, 1969
- Situation in Italy Will Get Much Worse, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois) June 2, 1970
- Some Youths Lack of Logic Baffling, The San Diego Union (Calif.) October 20, 1969
- Soviet Communism - 50 Years Later, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), November 5, 1967
- Soviet East Europe Power, The Sacramento Union (Calif.), August 9, 1968
- Soviet Espionage Again in Western Limelight, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), January 12, 1968
- Soviet Headaches, Joliet Herald-News (Illinois), February 18, 1970
- Soviet Military Budgets Are Difficult to Unravel, Aurora Beacon-News (Illinois), January 13, 1969
- Soviet Physicist Attacks Kremlin, The San Diego Union (Calif.), July 26, 1972
- Soviet System Compared With Old Czarist Movement, Springfield State Journal (Illinois), June 2, 1967
- Soviet Union's Actions Disillusioning to Many, The San Diego Union (Calif.), June 28, 1967